- - - - - -你好。-菲利普·卡尔弗特。
- Hello. - Well, Philip Calvert.
你看起来很好。马耳他怎么样?
You look well. How was Malta?
比这里暖和多了。你好吗?
A bloody sight warmer than here. How are you?
你看起来聪明。好的服装津贴在智力。
You look smart. Good clothing allowance in Intelligence.
我们有笔和回形针的零花钱。
We get an allowance for pens and paper clips.
每个文件柜后面都潜伏着危险。
Ah, danger lurks behind every filing cabinet.
在总部感觉如何?
How's it feel to be at Headquarters?
地中海舰队将举步维艰。我为什么在这里?
The Mediterranean fleet will be floundering. Why am I here?
-好吧，先生-其实这是我的主意
- All right, sir. - That was my idea, actually.
我们遇到了这样的问题，你看，你对航海，水下之类的东西这么在行。
We've got this sort of problem, you see, and you being so clever with nautical things, underwater and all that.
-你是说如果天湿了，我就是你的人。-可以这么说。
- You mean if it's wet, I'm your man. - So to speak.
我要成为世界上第一个水下间谍吗?
So am I going to be the world's first underwater spy?
这是有趣的。我很喜欢这样。不。是关于这些船的。金银器皿。
That's funny. I like that. No. It's about these ships. Bullion vessels.
从地球表面或公海上被劫持。
Hijacked off the face of the earth or rather the high seas.
——谁?人类的流亡者?请- - -菲利普。
- Who by? Human exiles? - Philip, please.
正如他们所说，这是一件事关国家的大事。
It is, as they say, a matter of national importance.
我觉得这个国家根本不在乎。这不是他们的黄金。
I doubt the nation gives a damn. It's not their gold.
每次都是同样的故事。船员们在爱尔兰的某个地方上岸，然后放了船，然后船就被带到天知道哪里去了。
The same story each time. Crews put ashore in some place in Ireland then released, by which time the ships are taken to God knows where.
我们应该做些什么来为民主拯救国家?
What are we supposed to do to save the nation for democracy?
我们两个人，菲利普——以我的组织才能和你的身体才能——我们必须制定出一个宏伟的计划，交给局长。
Between the two of us, Philip - with my organisational genius and your physical talents - we must evolve a master plan to take before the chief.
-谁是谁?- Arthur Arnford-Jones KCB爵士等等。
- Which is whom? - Sir Arthur Arnford-Jones KCB etcetera.
是的。相当令人印象深刻的记录……我想。
Yes. Quite an impressive record... I suppose.
我看到像所有在高度专业化部门工作的人一样，你对权威持怀疑态度。
I see that like all men employed in highly-specialised branches, you have a questionable attitude towards authority.
我不知道我是否喜欢。
I don't know that I care for that.
这里写着，不适合常规调查。
It says here, "Unsuitable for routine investigation.
“在极端压力下工作最好。
"Operates best under extreme pressure.
“在这个层面上，他是独一无二的。”你认为这是真的吗?
"At this level, he's unique." Do you suppose that's true?
-如果档案里有，那肯定是。-我不太高兴…是的。坐下来。我很不高兴，卡尔弗特。
- It must be if it's on the file. - I'm not happy about this... Yes. Do sit down. I'm not happy about this, Calvert.
当然，我更希望我的手下有查恩利勋爵和劳埃德银行的帮助。
I should have preferred my own men with the assistance of Lord Charnley and Lloyds, of course.
所有人都在盯着我。
I have everybody breathing down my neck.
海军部、政府、美国人和保险评估员——都是穿着华达呢雨衣、满身头皮屑的邋遢小人。
The Admiralty, the government, the Americans and the insurance assessors - grubby little men with gabardine raincoats and dandruff.
我没有头皮屑，先生。
I don't have dandruff, sir.
你不需要这么早就向权威表明你的可疑态度。
You don't need to demonstrate your questionable attitude to authority quite so early.
你和呃先生有什么…-汉斯莱特，先生-汉斯莱特
Well, what have you and Mr er... - Hunslett, sir. - Hunslett.
Hunslett。
Hunslett.
你想到什么了?
What have you come up with?
正确的。就是这个。
Right. It's this.
我们在下一艘金条船上藏两个人和一个发射器，这样如果她被劫持了我们就能知道她在哪里。
Let's conceal two men with a transmitter on the next bullion ship, so if she's hijacked we'll know where she is.
人们可以在预定的时间和频率发送信号我们可以测量方位。
The men can send signals at prearranged times and frequencies and we can take bearings.
也许汉斯莱特先生和我可以跟着这艘船。
It may be that Mr Hunslett and myself could then shadow the ship.
人能这样隐蔽吗?这似乎有些牵强。
Could men be concealed like that? It seems rather far-fetched.
我不喜欢它。太危险了。太多的“如果”和“但是”。
I don't like it. It's too dangerous. Too many ifs and buts.
恕我直言，你还没有"如果"和"但是"
With all due respect, you haven't had an if or a but.
下一艘船是南斯维尔号。
The next ship is the Nanceville.
价值八百万英镑的金条。
Eight million quids' worth of gold bullion.
这值得你冒一两次险吗?
Surely that's worth a risk or two?
-我坚持用我自己的人。——好的。
- I insist on using my own men. - OK.
我遇见他们。他们应该能照顾好自己。
I met them. They should be able to take care of themselves.
他们是很优秀的男人。他们当然能照顾好自己。
They're excellent men. They can certainly look after themselves.
-让他们进来，先生……——Hunslett。
- Show them in, Mr... - Hunslett.
进来,先生们。
Come in, gentlemen.
——亨利!在这里,很快。——Voltec。你绕到后面去。
- Henry! Up here, quickly. - Voltec. You go round the back.
来吧!
Come on!
接他。
Pick him up.
怎么样?
How did it go?
不好的。
Not good.
-我们脱掉这身盔甲吧-有什么不好的?
- Let's get out of this armour. - What was not good about it?
-太强烈的反对。-他们都是好人
- Too strong an opposition. - They were good men.
-敌人更好。-亚瑟叔叔不会喜欢的。
- The enemy were better. - Uncle Arthur won't like this.
-你觉得我喜欢吗?-我们的计划到此为止。
- Do you think I like it? - So much for our plan.
他们能发送信号，我们也能追踪到。
They were able to transmit and we were able to follow.
如果不考虑生命损失的话，这一切都是合理的。
It was all justified - if you discount loss of life, that is.
——对吗?-不，我没有。这是麻烦的。
- Do you? - No, I don't. That's the trouble.
在这里。我做了些喝的。
Here. I made something to drink.
-你今晚过得很不顺。-我是智慧，不是吗?
- You've been having a hard night. - I'm Intelligence, aren't I?
我得待在家里思考而你出去执行。
I have to stay in and think while you go out and implement.
我被勒死，被踢死而你却坐在这里…血腥的可可。
I get half strangled and kicked to death while you sit here making... bloody cocoa.
这是我擅长的。
It's what I do well.
我们喝点威士忌吧。
Let's have some whisky.
你最好给我的腿包扎一下。
You'd better bandage my leg.
我们可不想血溅一地，对吧?
We don't want blood all over the floor, do we?
-你想来点吗?——没有。
- Do you want some? - No.
天知道南斯维尔号现在已经在去哪里的路上了。
The Nanceville will be halfway to God knows where by now.
是的,我知道。但他们一开始确实来过这里，所以我们可以假设这片区域很重要，他们可能在这片区域有人。
Yes, I know. But they did come here in the first place, so we could assume that the area's significant and they could have people in the area.
我们是新到托贝的。
And we're new arrivals in Torbay.
全能的上帝!你对我的伤害比船上那个混蛋还严重。
God Almighty! You're hurting me more than that bastard on the ship.
对不起。我们在情报局没学过急救。
Sorry. We didn't learn first aid in Intelligence.
-够紧吗?好吗?-是的。
- Is that tight enough? OK? - Yeah.
谢谢。
Thanks.
现在几点了?
What time is it?
6:25。我们八点钟要用无线电通知亚瑟叔叔。
他的确很早去上班。
He does get to work early.
-早上好，先生-金凤花有消息吗
- Good morning, sir. - Any news from Buttercup?
——毛茛属植物?——黛西。
- Buttercup? - Daisy.
你是说卡洛琳吧，先生，随时奉陪。
Oh, you mean Caroline, sir. Any moment now.
“我是安娜贝利，打电话给卡洛琳。使用扰频程序。”
'This is Annabel calling Caroline. Use the scrambler procedure.'
早上好。这是卡洛琳。我可以和安娜贝尔通话吗?
Good morning. This is Caroline. May I speak to Annabel?
早上好,卡洛琳。这是安娜贝利。
Good morning, Caroline. This is Annabel.
481.281位置。
Location 481.281.
苏格兰西部。一个叫休伦湖的地方。”
'West of Scotland. A place called Loch Huron.'
我有你。你找到失踪的船只了吗?
I have you. Have you located the missing vessel?
——“我有。“——在哪儿?”
- 'I have.' - Where is it?
你是说它在哪里?现在可能有一百英里远了。
Where was it, you mean. Could be a hundred miles away by now.
不同的颜色，不同的标记，不同的旗帜。
Different colours, different markings, different flags.
“我们的朋友怎么办?”
'What about our friends? '
他们不会回家了。我已经在船上了，但我是被期待的。
They won't be coming home. I've been aboard but I was expected.
“我警告过你，卡罗琳。”
'I warned you about this, Caroline.'
菲尔!某人的到来。
Phil! Someone's coming.
-“你把整件事都搞砸了。-必须收拾行李。
- 'You've messed up the whole thing.' - Must pack up.
你可能拥有的任何有用或有效的东西都已经消失了。
Any usefulness or effectiveness you might have had has been dissipated.
现在不能说话。
Can't talk now.
我们失去了两个朋友。我们失去了那艘船。
We've lost two friends. We've lost the vessel.
-我们失去了秘密。-我们跟丢了，长官。
- We've lost the secrecy. - We've lost him, sir.
卡尔弗特吗?卡尔弗特!
Calvert? Calvert!
快点!
Hurry!
早上好,先生们。你把牛奶带来了吗?
Morning, gentlemen. Have you brought the milk?
早....我是托贝警察局的麦克唐纳警官。
Morning. I'm Sergeant MacDonald from Torbay police station.
-这些先生是海关官员。——是吗?这是一种有趣的生活。
- These gentlemen are Customs officials. - Are they? That's an interesting life.
-这是你的船吗，先生?-是的。或者说，这是我雇主的。
- Is this your boat, sir? - Yes, it is. Or rather it's my employer's.
-那是谁?——政府。
- And who is that? - The government.
——政府?——是的。你没看到国旗吗?
- The government? - Yes. Didn't you see the flag?
农业水产部。海洋生物学家。
Ministry of Agriculture and Fisheries. Marine biologists.
我们就像是一个漂浮的实验室。各种奇怪的标本。
We're a kind of floating laboratory. All sorts of odd specimens.
我们在找昨晚在埃尔郡被盗的化学品。
We're looking for chemicals that were stolen from Ayrshire last night.
显然他们是从海上来的。
Apparently they came north by sea.
这是我们检查的第三个港口，也是第13艘船。
This is the third port we've checked and the 13th boat.
只是例行公事，你看。
Just routine, you see.
你一定累坏了。
You must be exhausted.
你为什么不到下面来呢?我的朋友做的可可非常好。
Why don't you come below - my friend makes very good cocoa.
——干杯。——谢谢。
- Cheers. - Thank you.
我可以复印这些吗?——确定。
- Might I photocopy these? - Sure.
-是的，我有一台便携式复印机。——好的。
- Yes, I have a portable photocopier. - OK.
-欢迎你四处看看。-我觉得没必要。
- You're welcome to look around. - I don't think that's necessary.
我想看看引擎室。
I'd like to see the engine rooms.
也许汉斯莱特先生会带中士去生活区?
Perhaps Mr Hunslett will show the Sergeant the living quarters?
这里
This way.
你带了很多电池。为什么要这么强大?
You carry a lot of batteries. Why all the power?
我们在实验室里有八个电动机，当我们在港口的时候这意味着我们不能用这些发动机来为它们提供动力。
We've got eight electric motors in the lab for when we're in harbour which means we can't use the engines to supply the juice for them.
还有中央供暖、热水和电动绞车。
Then there's the central heating, hot water and the electric winches.
当然，还有我的电动牙刷。
And, of course, my electric toothbrush.
是的,当然。船不是我的职业。
Yes, of course. Boats aren't really my line.
法律是真实的。你模仿警察不可能模仿得那么好。
The law were genuine. You can't imitate coppers as good as that.
海关没有。他们说他们坐过13艘船。
The Customs weren't. They said they'd been on 13 boats.
它们看起来像是从洗衣店买来的。
They look like they've come from the cleaners.
一个说:“船不是我的职业。”这是什么话?
One said, "Boats aren't my line." What sort of remark is that?
就像亚瑟叔叔说他从没听说过板球一样。
It's like Uncle Arthur saying he's never heard of cricket.
我再告诉你一件事。他们没有复印机。
I'll tell you something else. They didn't have a photocopier.
啊。不尊重别人的财产。
Ah. No respect for other people's property.
上面全是血。他一定是受伤了。
There's blood all over it. He must have hurt himself.
所以他才没摘下手套。他的手受伤了。
That's why he didn't take his gloves off. He hurt his hand.
——是吗?——是的。我用刀捅了进去。
- Did he? - Yes. I shoved a knife through it.
昨晚在南斯维尔。
Last night on the Nanceville.
——是吗?——是的。
- Did you? - Yes.
-再见。——好的。
- See you later. - OK.
——早上好。——早上好。
- Good morning. - Good morning.
你带来了很好的天气。
You've no' brought very nice weather with you.
我可以用一下你的电话吗?长途。
May I use your phone? Long distance.
-没有一个电话能用。-最近的电话在哪里?
- None of the phones are working. - Where's the nearest phone?
大陆但船已经开了。
The mainland. But the boat's sailed.
四天后才会回来。
It won't be back for four days.
嗯，我最好储备一些烟草。可能是漫长的冬天。
Well, I'd better stock up on some tobacco. Could be a long winter.
你在这找不到多少海洋标本，卡尔弗特先生。
You'll not find many marine specimens up here, Mr Calvert.
只是运动一下，中士。
Just getting some exercise, Sergeant.
被困在船上，我只想活动活动腿。
Cooped up on that boat, I just want to stretch my legs.
从托贝到这里有很长一段路。
It's a long stretch from Torbay.
不过，这对一个人来说是好事。美妙的空气。
Good for one, though. Wonderful air.
那些电线真可怜。我不知道昨晚有暴风雨。
Pity about those wires. Didn't know it was stormy last night.
如果你在那条船上，你肯定感觉到了吧?
Surely you felt it if you were in that boat?
-顺便说一下，我们的收音机被砸了。——是吗?香格里拉也是如此。
- By the way, our radio was smashed. - Was it? So was the Shangri-la.
-我们会调查的。-这让人安心。
- We'll be looking into it. - That is reassuring.
-谁在香格里拉?-安东尼·斯古洛斯爵士
- Who's on the Shangri-la? - Sir Anthony Skouras.
斯古洛斯那个船夫?大油性塞浦路斯吗?
Skouras the shipping man? Big oily Cypriot?
安东尼爵士。没人比他更仁慈了。
SIR Anthony. There's not a kinder man sailed into Torbay.
没有犯罪。好老Skouras。
No offence. Good old Skouras.
你最好不要冒犯他的名字，尤其是在我面前。
You'd be as well not to offend his name, especially in front of me.
去年，我不幸失去了两个儿子，在我们悲痛的时候，安东尼爵士对我们非常好。
I lost two sons tragically last year and Sir Anthony was most kind to us in our time of grief.
祝你好运。
Good day to you.
这是开证!我们会一直关注你。
That's for openers! We'll be watching you.
我希望你能学到一些东西!
I hope you learn something!
我不是发现了一些事情吗?
Haven't I found out some things!
你在酒吧待多久了?
How long have you been in the pub?
我不得不。我需要几杯威士忌来让当地人放松一下。
I had to. I needed a few whiskies to get the locals to loosen up.
我将索赔费用。
I'll claim expenses.
不像苏格兰人那样热情好客吧?你发现了什么?
Not full of Scottish hospitality, are they? What did you find out?
首先，这是一个事故多发的地区。
Firstly, it's an accident-prone area.
海上灾难，死亡，失踪——船，游艇。
Disasters at sea, deaths, disappearances - boats, yachts.
我想知道确切的时间。还有什么?
Exactly when, I wonder. What else?
岸上也发生了很多个人悲剧。你知道那艘船是谁的吗?
A lot of personal tragedy ashore too. You know who that boat belongs to?
——Skouras。我知道。——哦。
- Skouras. I know. - Oh.
你发现了什么?你怎么这么邋遢?
What have you discovered? Why are you so messy?
我在石南丛中碰到了一个吉普赛人女孩，仅此而已。
I bumped into this wild gypsy girl in the heather, that's all.
菲尔,看。
Phil, look.
-他们在发什么信号?——嗯…情报组没教过我们这些。
- What are they signalling? - Um... They didn't teach us that in Intelligence.
让我们看看…有什么消息吗?
Let's see... What's the message?
消息读取…十点喝酒。
Message reads... drinks at ten o'clock.
这很好。谢谢你！
That's fine. Thank you.
-就像苏富比拍卖行一样。-人们是怎么变得这么有钱的?
- It's like Sotheby's afloat. - How do people get this rich?
也许他们劫持了金条船。
Maybe they hijack bullion ships.
我们站错边了，不是吗?
We're on the wrong side, aren't we?
只有一方可以支持——获胜的一方。
There's only one side to be on - the winning one.
我的道歉,先生们。我的歉意。
My apologies, gentlemen. My apologies.
我们把商务和晚餐结合在一起，这不仅不礼貌，而且不利于消化。
We were combining business with dinner, which is not only impolite but bad for the digestion.
-我是菲利普·卡尔弗特-你好!
- I'm Philip Calvert. - How do you do?
-这是我朋友罗伊·汉斯莱特-你好!
- This is my friend Roy Hunslett. - How do you do?
我们想是时候见见我们的新邻居了。
We thought it was time to meet our new neighbours.
请允许我介绍拉沃斯基先生，麦克勒姆先生…哦，还有斯古洛斯夫人。
May I introduce Mr Lavorski, Mr Macullum... Oh, and Lady Skouras.
我应该先介绍你的，亲爱的。
I should have introduced you first, darling.
你应该这么做，但你很少这么做。
You should have but you rarely do.
——夏洛特。——夫人Skouras。
- Charlotte. - Lady Skouras.
夏洛特。
Charlotte.
-你好!-你好!
- How do you do? - How do you do?
嗯哼。你们喜欢喝威士忌还是喝白兰地?
Ahem. Would you chaps prefer to stay with whisky or would you like a brandy?
我们就喝威士忌吧，谢谢。
We'll stick to whisky, thank you.
我们吃过我朋友做的豆子吐司和冷冻牛肉汉堡。
We've dined on my friend's beans on toast and frozen beefburgers.
白兰地根本没机会了。
The brandy wouldn't stand a chance.
我也要喝威士忌。但是出于沙文主义。
I'll stick to whisky too. But out of chauvinism.
你觉得这个地方怎么样?对你来说够湿吗?
How do you like this part of the world? Is it wet enough for you?
我们在工作，所以没什么大不了的。
Well, we're working, so it doesn't very much matter.
-他们是海洋生物学家。-消息传得很快。
- They're marine biologists. - Word gets round very quickly.
安东尼爵士知道托贝发生的一切。
Sir Anthony knows everything that goes on in Torbay.
他来这里已经好几季了。
He's been cruising here for several seasons.
法国南部和爱琴海根本比不上这片水域。
The South of France and the Aegean can't hold a candle to these waters.
这是真的。
That's true.
当你在这里可以忍受一个月的寒风和雨水的时候，谁想在那么无聊的阳光下环游希腊群岛呢?
Who wants to cruise around the Greek Isles in all that boring sunshine when you can have a month of freezing wind and rain up here?
夏洛特对游艇的想法是把一个昂贵的漂浮衣橱永久地系在码头上。
Charlotte's idea of yachting is an expensive floating wardrobe permanently moored to a quay.
-最好是在蔚蓝海岸。——最好。
- Preferably on the Cфte d'Azur. - Preferably.
一群晒成古铜色的年轻人在秀他们的发型。
With a lot of bronzed young men flexing their hairdos.
原谅的牢骚。我们要举办一个代沟之夜。
Excuse the bitching. We're having one of our generation gap evenings.
过来,夏洛特。一年也就几个星期而已。
Come along, Charlotte. It's only a few weeks a year.
-你知道安东尼有多喜欢这里。-他也是
- You know how Anthony loves it here. - He does too.
安东尼爵士在这方面做了很多善事。
Sir Anthony has done many fine and charitable things in this area.
是的。我听说了
Yes. So I hear.
好的工作和公共服务对富人来说非常容易。
Good works and public services are very easy for the rich.
-就像签支票一样简单。——夏洛特。
- As easy as signing a cheque. - Charlotte.
-我认为这很不公平。-把那张照片拿来。
- I think that's rather unfair. - Fetch me that picture.
拜托。
Please.
你们看，先生们，尽管夏洛特愤世嫉俗，我的动机是完全真诚的。
You see, gentlemen, despite Charlotte's cynicism, my motives were completely genuine.
我的妻子……我的第一任妻子，安娜。
My wife... Um, that is, my first wife, Anna.
多年前，我和妻子在度蜜月时对苏格兰的这一地区产生了感情。
My wife and I grew attached to this part of Scotland on our honeymoon many years ago.
签支票从来不是件容易的事，卡尔弗特先生。
And it's never easy to sign a cheque, Mr Calvert.
尤其是当你很有钱的时候。
Especially when you're rich.
看到另一半如何航行总是好的。
It's always good to see how the other half sail.
很高兴看到你的另一半看到你的另一半。
It's nice to see the other half seeing the other half.
也许我们应该为那些在海上遇险的人干杯。
Perhaps we should drink to those in peril on the sea.
-我们有危险吗?-这片水域总是充满危险
- Are we in peril? - There's always peril in these waters.
欢呼。
Cheers.
身体健康。
Good health.
良好的财富。
Good wealth.
卡洛琳。卡洛琳。这里是SFPX站。
Calling Caroline. Caroline. This is Station SFPX.
再重复一遍,SFPX。你听到了吗?
Repeat, SFPX. Are you receiving me?
重复。你听到了吗?结束了。
Repeat. Are you receiving me? Over.
你应该用无线电通知亚瑟叔叔。
You should have radioed Uncle Arthur.
等待不会伤害他的。他可以在俱乐部再喝一瓶波尔图葡萄酒。
The wait won't hurt him. He can have another bottle of port at the club.
-绳子紧吗?-我想是的。
- Is that rope tight? - I think so.
我不太擅长打结。
I'm not awfully good at knots.
我知道，情报组可没教你这些。
I know, they didn't teach you that at Intelligence.
血腥的家伙。英格兰北部文法学校。
Bloody fellow. North of England grammar school.
"在各行各业辛勤工作"的那种。
"Working his way through the ranks of life" type.
——没有背景。-也许出了什么问题。
- No background. - Perhaps something's gone wrong.
我们不必赶着吃晚饭。我讨厌赶着吃饭。
We needn't have rushed dinner. I hate rushing dinner.
也许他有危险。
Maybe he's in some danger.
我可能吃过斯蒂尔顿奶酪。
I might have tried some of that Stilton.
注意，你永远不会知道……什么?
Mind you, you never know... What?
我说他可能有危险。
I said he may be in some danger.
-受伤了还是怎么的-希望不是什么小事。
- Got hurt or something. - Let's hope it's nothing trivial.
现在我们知道为什么像我们这样的小混混会被请去喝酒了。
Now we know why scruffs like us were asked over for drinks.
最好接通鼓风机。
Better get on the blower.
打扰一下，先生，我是卡罗琳。
Excuse me, sir. Caroline calling.
它从不停止。来吧。
It never stops. Come on.
这里有一艘船，肯定有关联。
There's a boat here with a definite connection.
他们的发射机也被砸了但那可能是个幌子。
They had their transmitter smashed too but that could be a cover.
他们请我们去喝酒。总之，他们搜查了火rest。
They had us over for drinks. Anyway, they searched the Firecrest.
奇怪的设置。一对无法忍受彼此的夫妻还有一个管住他们的男人。
Strange setup. A husband and wife who can't stand each other and a man who presides over them.
“丈夫叫斯古洛斯。安东尼爵士Skouras。”
'The husband's name is Skouras. Sir Anthony Skouras.'
你不知道他是谁吗?
Don't you know who he is?
-“一个有前科的人……-好吧，好吧。
- 'A man with his record... ' - All right, all right.
这是不对的。
It's not all right.
他是我们俱乐部的杰出成员。
He's a distinguished member of my own club.
他是葡萄酒委员会的成员!
He's on the wine committee!
恕我直言，安娜贝尔，先生，没必要心跳骤停因为我不像你那样相信你的同伴们是正直的。
With all due respect, Annabel, sir, there's no need to go into cardiac arrest because I don't share your faith in the probity of your fellow members.
那就够了。
That'll be quite enough of that.
明天中午到这里报到。直升机将在5点来接你。
Report here at noon tomorrow. A helicopter will pick you up at five.
先生，让我留下来，直到我至少…我不这么认为，毛茛。
Sir, let me stay on until I can at least... I think not, Buttercup.
你越早停止转移话题，对我们大家都好。
The sooner you stop chasing red herrings, the better for all of us.
至少帮我查一下事实。
At least check some facts for me.
-很好，如果它们是有效的。——在这里。
- Very well, if they're valid. - Here.
绝望的家伙。因为没有上正规的学校。
Hopeless fellow. Comes of not going to a proper school.
纸在哪里?你这样做。卡罗琳,继续。
Where's the paper? You do it. Carry on, Caroline.
哦。卡洛琳。
Oh. Caroline.
火。
Fire ahead.
-没有改变主意?——没有。值得一试。
- No second thoughts? - No. It's worth a chance.
我只会失去我的工作。
All I've got to lose is my job.
我希望这就是你的全部损失，你这个疯狂的混蛋。欢呼。
I hope that's all you lose, you mad bastard. Cheers.
——早上。-威廉姆斯中尉。卡尔弗特吗?
- Morning. - Lieutenant Williams. You Calvert?
——指挥官卡尔弗特。-对不起，先生
- Commander Calvert. - Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
没关系。我摆架子是因为我要改变你的命令。
That's all right. I'm pulling rank because I'm changing your orders.
-你很熟悉这一带?- - - - - -很好。
- You know this area well? - Very well.
-但我要带你去伦敦。——先生。
- But I'm meant to take you to London. - Sir.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
我们改天再去伦敦。我承担全部责任。好吗?
We'll go to London some other time. I take full responsibility. OK?
好的，先生，我是说，是的，先生。
OK, sir. I mean - yes, sir.
好。
Good.
-抽根烟。忘了那些先生们吧。——谢谢。
- Have a cigarette. Forget about the sirs. - Thanks.
我需要一个搜查这片区域的借口。
I need an excuse to search the area.
你能用无线电发出假求救信号吗?
Can you put out a false Mayday on your radio?
-我想让BBC接收它。——你在开玩笑吧?
- I want the BBC to pick it up. - You're kidding?
——中尉。-是的，长官，可以的，长官。
- Lieutenant. - Yes, sir. It can be done, sir.
“…克莱德造船厂的质量才能维持下去
'... could the quality of the Clyde shipyards be maintained.
“一艘船在斯凯岛附近遇到了麻烦。
'A boat is in trouble near the island of Skye.
“今天早上从TSDY Moray Rose号上接收到一个求救信号，”报告说“不受控制，水流湍急。”
'A distress signal was picked up this morning from the TSDY Moray Rose, 'reported not under command and making water fast.
已向空中和海上救援机构发出警报
'Air sea rescue services have been alerted.'
我们走吧。
Let's go.
我在找一个藏身之处。可能还有一艘船。
I'm looking for a hide-out. Probably a boat as well.
汽艇之类的。可能是一个大的船库。
A motor launch or something. Might be a big boathouse.
甚至可能是一个小港口。
Might even be a tiny harbour.
在艾雷岛和斯凯岛之间。
Somewhere between Islay and Skye.
不可能超过一千英里的海岸线。午饭后我们做什么?
Can't be more than 1,000 miles of coastline. What do we do after lunch?
-我们去那边看看。——好的。
- Let's have a look at that over there. - OK.
好的。
OK.
皇家海军直升机。
Royal Navy helicopter.
那架直升机不是在监视。这是空中海上救援。
That helicopter's not spying. It's Air Sea Rescue.
我听说有艘船失踪了。
I heard something about a missing boat.
也许他会把我从这种单调的生活中解救出来。
Perhaps he'll rescue me from this monotony.
我可以给你很多建议，让你从这种单调中解脱出来。
I could suggest many ways you could rescue yourself from this monotony.
闭嘴!这两个你。
Shut up! Both of you.
Craigmuir港口。
Craigmuir Harbour.
-他们是捕鲸者吗?- - - - - -鲨鱼。
- Are they whale hunters? - Sharks.
用于鱼肝油。我去过一次。我为他们担保。
For the liver oil. I've been there once. I'd vouch for them.
老板叫蒂姆·哈钦森。
Boss goes by the name of Tim Hutchinson.
我们去打个招呼吧。
Let's go and say hello.
-你是哈钦森吗?——啊。
- Are you Hutchinson? - Aye.
我叫卡尔弗特，海空救援。
My name's Calvert, Air Sea Rescue.
你们有谁想获救吗?
Any of you lads want to be rescued?
不。我觉得没人想被救，谢谢。
No. I don't think anyone wants to be rescued, thank you.
-就凭这味道?什么气味?
- Even from that smell? - What smell?
听着，你能帮我吗?
Listen, can you help me?
在过去的几个月里你在这附近看到过什么奇怪的船吗?
Have you seen any strange boats in the area over the last few months?
半隐蔽还是停泊?
Half hidden or moored?
-没有，但我们会留意的。——谢谢。
- No, but we'll keep our eyes open. - Thanks.
-有卡尔弗特的消息吗?-恐怕不行，先生。
- Any news of Calvert? - I'm afraid not, sir.
那个该死的家伙怎么了?
What's happened to the bloody fellow?
我只知道我们还没有接到直升机的消息。
All I Know is we haven't heard from the helicopter.
你没有正经的饼干吗?——对不起,先生?
- Haven't you any proper biscuits? - Pardon, sir?
里面有奶油的饼干。不要紧。
Proper biscuits with cream inside. Never mind.
——这是什么?-你要的信息，先生。
- What's this? - The information you asked for, sir.
看看这个地方。它叫Baile nan Ui。
Look at this place. It's called Baile nan Ui.
什么?
What?
佰乐南Ui。盖尔语。它的意思是“坟墓之口”。
Baile nan Ui. It's Gaelic. It means the "mouth of the grave".
休伦尼斯。
Loch Huron.
那里的城堡叫杜·斯凯。柯克塞德勋爵的家。
That castle there is called Du Skea. Home of Lord Kirkside.
马上回来。
Be back in a minute.
你的引擎出故障了吗?-空中海上救援，小姐…呃?
- Have you got engine failure? - Air Sea Rescue, Miss... er?
这不是海，这是私人土地。
This isn't sea, this is private land.
为什么当地人这么不友好?我只想问几个问题。
Why are the natives so hostile? I only want to ask a few questions.
-你老爸呢?-我想你是说柯克塞德勋爵吧?
- Where's your old man? - I assume you mean Lord Kirkside?
如果你是女儿，是的。你老爸呢?
If you're the daughter, yes. Where's your old man?
老人在这里。Kirkside。
The old man's over here. Kirkside.
卡尔弗特。有一艘船叫“马里玫瑰号”……我听说了这个消息。这附近没有她的踪迹。
Calvert. There's a boat called the Moray Rose... I heard the news. There's no sign of her round here.
没有耀斑。今天早上我自己在悬崖周围看了看。
No flares. I took a look round the cliffs myself this morning.
——好的。很抱歉突然来访。-你看…我儿子和苏的fiancй…他们最近在一次飞行事故中失踪了。
- OK. Sorry about dropping in. - You see... My son and Sue's fiancй... they disappeared recently in a flying accident.
总是有很多媒体人来串门。
There's been a lot of press men always dropping in.
我明白了。对不起。
I understand. Sorry.
天快黑了。
We're running out of daylight.
飞越岛屿的北端，然后回家。
Fly over the northern end of the island and then home.
天有点黑了。地面应该是湿的。
It's getting a bit dark. The ground should be soggy.
我在空中盘旋，你跳，长官。
So I'll hover, you jump, sir.
保持下来。
Keep down.
-天啊，你动作真快。-是的…
- My God, you move fast. - Yeah...
他现在不会上来了。我们走吧。
He won't be coming up now. Let's go.
Hunslett吗?
Hunslett?
Hunslett !
Hunslett!
Hunslett吗?
Hunslett?
-我有枪。-让我起来!
- I've got a gun. - Let me up!
你可能会死的。在你的右边，有一个电灯开关。
You could be a dead man. On your right, there's a light switch.
慢慢地打开开关。
Very slowly, switch it on.
谢谢你，卡尔弗特先生。
Thank you, Mr Calvert.
我已经抓到你的无礼，违抗命令和不服从。
I've already got you for insolence, insubordination and disobedience.
现在是武装袭击。你总是这样跟客人打招呼吗?
Now it's armed assault. Do you always greet your guests like this?
我没有客人。我没有朋友。我只有敌人。
I don't have guests. I don't have friends. I only have enemies.
不要站在那儿。给我一杯威士忌加苏打。
Don't stand there. Get me a whisky and soda.
我坐皇家空军的飞机来的。
I came by RAF plane and launch.
那些该死的人给我的都是茶包。Hunslett在哪?
All the bloody people offered me were tea bags. Where's Hunslett?
我最后一次见到他是今天早上。
The last time I saw him was this morning.
我希望什么都没发生。我们不能再损失人员了。
I hope nothing's happened. We can't afford to lose any more personnel.
人员吗?
Personnel?
他与我无关。他是我过去十年的朋友。
He's not personnel to me. He's been my friend for the last ten years.
我还要告诉你一件事。
And I'll tell you another thing.
你可以为你因公殉职的次数再添一笔。
You can add another statistic to your deaths in the line of duty.
直升机飞行员。
The helicopter pilot.
感谢上帝，你没有把我的也算进去。
It's only by the grace of God you're not adding mine to it.
你被命令回来。你违背了。
You were ordered to return. You disobeyed.
我用了更好的判断力。
I used my better judgment.
作为当时在场的人，我认为自己的判断比坐在英国白厅(Whitehall)优雅办公室里的人的判断更切合实际。
As the person on the spot, I considered my judgment more relevant that that of people sitting in elegant Whitehall offices.
冷静下来。我理解你的感受。你说的对。
Calm down. I understand your feelings. You're right about the area.
你让我启动的那些轮子，我已经想到了答案。
Those wheels you asked me to set in motion, I've come up with answers.
-这仍然是你的工作，卡尔弗特-谢谢你，先生。
- It's still your job, Calvert. - Thank you, sir.
现在。你想知道海岸附近失踪船只的情况。
Now then. You wanted to know about missing vessels around these coasts.
9月4日。平托-巡洋舰。
September 4th. Pinto - cruiser.
离开洛迦什的凯尔去了阿伦。消失了。
Left the Kyles of Lochalsh for Arran. Vanished.
假种皮6日。晚上的明星。4月10日。珍妮玫瑰。渔船。
Aril 6th. Evening Star. April 10th. Jenny Rose. Both fishing boats.
5月17日。来自伦敦德里郡的经验丰富的船员。
May 17th. Sailing boat with highly experienced crew from Londonderry.
几周前，从托贝出发的翠鸟号夜间巡航。
A few weeks ago, the Kingfisher, on a night cruise from Torbay.
日期呢?
What about the dates?
都发生在金条船失踪的48小时内。
All within 48 hours of the disappearance of the bullion ships.
陆地上的事故太多了。
There've been too many accidents on land.
一个警察和他的家人，一个乡绅和他的家人。
A policeman and his family, the local squire and his family.
还有柯克塞德勋爵。你认识他吗?
And a Lord Kirkside. Do you know him?
我在书上读到过。我想我们大概见过一次。
I read about that. I think we met once, vaguely.
皮布尔斯猎松鸡。
Grouse shooting in Peebles.
那名字呢，拉沃斯基和lmrie?
What about the names - Lavorski and lmrie?
我走之前什么都没发生。
Nothing came up before I left.
喂，这船上有什么好吃的吗?
I say, do you have anything palatable to eat on this boat?
bean。
Beans.
住宿呢?
What about sleeping accommodation?
我想我们不会睡着的。
I don't think we will be sleeping.
如果我们假设他们抓了亨斯莱特，他们也会假设抓到了我。
If we assume they've got Hunslett, they'll assume they've got me.
如果他们看到灯光，他们就会来拜访。
If they see lights, they'll come visiting.
-我们该怎么办?——我们将管理。
- What are we going to do? - We'll manage.
他们的到来。做好准备。
They're coming. Get ready.
-另一个呢?-大约20英寻以下。
- Where's the other one? - About 20 fathoms below.
你不能像一个人的行刑队一样到处跑。这是英格兰。
You can't go round like a one-man execution squad. This is England.
你坐在办公室里也挺好的。
It's all very well for you sitting in an office.
像我这样的人只是地图上的图钉。
People like me are just pins on a map.
这就是它的意义所在。不是他就是我。
That's what it's all about. It's either him or me.
我欣赏你的观点，但不喜欢你的态度。
I appreciate your point but not your manner.
-我们该拿他怎么办?把他交给警察。
- What do we do with him? - Hand him over to the police.
他把地毯弄得一团糟。
He's making a terrible mess of the carpet.
你为什么不去吃点东西呢?我去看看上帝。
Why don't you get something to eat? I'll check up on the lord.
-你不会再杀人了?-天啊，不。
- You won't kill anybody else? - Good Lord, no.
很好。我得吃点热的东西。
Good. I must get some hot food inside me.
该死的英国皇家空军和他们该死的奶酪卷。
Bloody RAF with their damn cheese rolls.
如果你有个对讲机，你就不用划船过河了。
If you got yourself a walkie-talkie, you wouldn't have to row across.
香格里拉。
The Shangri-la.
你那些最近死去的孩子呢?
How about these boys of yours that died recently?
你是谁?警察?
Who are you? Police?
排序的。我想你最好来看看我的一个朋友。
Sort of. I think you'd better come and see a friend of mine.
他们说要杀了我的孩子们。我别无选择。
They said they would kill my boys. I had no choice.
我只能跟着他们走。
I just have to string along with them.
比如把他们当海关人员带到你的船上砸收音机。
Like bringing them as Customs men to your boat to smash the radio.
比如当我看到这里发生的所有犯罪行为时保持沉默。
Like keeping silent when I see all the criminal goings-on around here.
人和船都消失了，你知道，有些船如果去了某些地方就会被撞坏。
People and boats disappear, you know, and some boats get smashed up if they go in certain places.
这是不可思议的。Skouras。
It's incredible. Skouras.
是的，长官，有个叫lmrie的上尉，还有个叫Quinn的…警官，让我告诉你一些残酷的现实。
Yes, sir. There's a Captain lmrie sometimes and a man called Quinn... Sergeant, let me give you some harsh facts of life.
我的同事失踪了，一名飞行员今天死了，我也该死了。
My colleague is missing, a pilot was killed today and I should have been.
48小时前，亚瑟爵士的两名特工在休伦湖的一艘船上被杀。
他们可能会保护你的孩子，也可能不会但你不能接受他们的承诺。
They may or may not have your boys in safe keeping but you can't afford to take promises from them.
-你得帮我们，快点。-你想让我做什么?
- You've got to help us, and fast. - What do you want me to do?
这是黎明。
It's the dawn.
我以前见过黎明，谢谢!
I've seen the dawn before, thank you!
鸭子射击，是吗?
Duck shooting, was it?
别这么无礼!
Don't be so bloody insolent!
尤其是在海上。尤其是在早餐前。
Especially at sea. Especially before breakfast.
的帮助!
Help!
-嘿，那是谁?-我不知道。来吧。
- Hey, who's that? - I've no idea. Come on.
的帮助!
Help!
好的。来吧。
All right. Come on.
好的。你是安全的。把手给我。
All right. You're safe. Give me your hand.
来吧。你来了。
Come on. Up you come.
来吧。
Come on.
我想警告你。
I wanted to warn you.
昨天晚上，那个警察——我想大家都叫他麦克唐纳——上了船。
Last night, the policeman - MacDonald, I think he's called - came aboard.
继续。
Go on.
当他离开时，他们——我是说我丈夫和其他人……-他们决定必须阻止你。——停止?
When he left, they - I mean my husband and the others... - They decided you must be stopped. - Stopped?
你们能明白我的心情
You know what I mean.
我早就知道出事了。
I've known for ages something was wrong.
——奇怪的旅程。奇怪的男人。-你为什么要警告我们?
- Strange journeys. Strange men aboard. - Why did you want to warn us?
——这是显而易见的。- - - - - -闭嘴!
- That's obvious. - Shut up!
继续。
Go on.
你是唯一在场的人。我必须离开那艘船。
You were the only one around. And I had to get off that boat.
——再一次,为什么?-我想看看另一半如何航行。
- Again, why? - I wanted to see how the other half sail.
你必须原谅卡尔弗特先生。他天生没有礼貌。
You must forgive Mr Calvert. He has naturally bad manners.
让我帮助。
Let me help.
亲爱的，你到这里来冒了很大的风险。
You took a great risk coming here, my dear.
我没有什么可失去的。
I had nothing to lose.
我们还会失去很多。
We've still got a lot to lose.
我们走吧。我们已经浪费了很多时间了。
Let's go. We've wasted enough time already.
你确定是休伦湖吗?
Are you sure it's Loch Huron?
Du Skea。必须通过排除的过程。
Du Skea. Must be by process of elimination.
这座城堡是天然的基地。有人用无线电说我在直升机里。
The castle's a natural base. Someone radioed that I was in the helicopter.
如果有更多的恐吓，这和柯克塞德的情况相符。
If there's more intimidation, it fits in with the Kirkside situation.
女儿的态度。
The daughter's attitude.
啊，我们有客人了。
Ah, we've got company.
他们来找我了。
They're coming for me.
打开驾驶室的门，把门锁上。
Open the wheelhouse door, keep it back on the latch.
轮。我一喊，掉头，然后关掉引擎。
Take the wheel. When I shout, turn it about, then cut the engine.
现在!
Now!
看出来。他要撞我们了!
Look out. He's going to ram us!
下来!
Down!
停止发动机。
Stop engines.
不敬虔的人越来越少了。
The ranks of the ungodly are being depleted.
杀戮不是为了保护我。
That killing isn't necessary just to protect me.
我也不知道，那是为了亨斯莱特。
Neither do I. That was to square things for Hunslett.
我们为什么要去杜·斯凯?还是让我管好自己的事?
Why are we going to Du Skea? Or do I mind my own business?
我再也受不了了。
I can't take much more of this.
我们要证明不列颠尼亚统治海上。
We're going to prove Britannia rules the waves.
我们盯上他们了，他们没有多少时间来抛售黄金。
We're onto them and it doesn't give them much time to unload their bullion.
-他们不能在这里卸货。——是的。休伦尼斯。
- They can't unload bullion here. - Yes. Loch Huron.
南斯维尔号这么大的货轮在休伦湖是藏不住的。
You can't hide a freighter the size of the Nanceville in Loch Huron.
把船藏起来很容易。打开海螺就行了。
It's easy to hide a ship. Just open the sea cocks.
他们不在休伦湖。他们在它。
They're not in Loch Huron. They're under it.
这个年轻女人做的。它应该是可以喝的。
The young woman made this. It ought to be drinkable.
-接通了吗?——是的。
- Did you get through? - Yes.
精神食粮。
Food for thought.
1963年，斯古洛斯航线(Skouras Line)的一艘豪华邮轮上有一位船长lmrie。
There was a Captain lmrie in charge of a Skouras Line ship - a liner on a luxury cruise in 1963.
她牺牲了70条生命。
She went down with 70 lives.
本来会有大麻烦的，但我为飞行员的错误承担了全部责任。有趣。
There would have been a big stink but lmrie took the whole rap for pilot error. Interesting.
我不太明白你指的是什么，不过没关系。继续。
I don't quite know what you're getting at but never mind. Go on.
我告诉他们安娜贝利很喜欢这次旅行。
I've told them that Annabel is enjoying the cruise.
是吗?
Did you?
跟我说说第一夫人斯古洛斯。她什么时候死的?
Tell me about the first Lady Skouras. When did she die?
大约一年前。
About a year ago.
——忠实的夫妇?-我一直这么认为。为什么?
- Devoted couple? - I always thought so. Why?
我在想现在的斯古洛斯夫人。
I'm wondering about the present Lady Skouras.
我想知道她是什么时候认识他的。
I wonder when she met him.
我得跟脸红的新娘说句话。
I must have a word with the blushing bride.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
开着这艘船去休伦湖想了解你。
Taking this boat to Loch Huron and trying to figure you out.
-我不知道哪个更难。,何苦呢?
- I don't know which is more difficult. - Why bother?
我想让自己安心。
I want to put my mind at ease.
没什么好知道的。
There's nothing to know.
我嫁给了一个千万富翁，结果发现他是个骗子。
I married a multi-millionaire who turns out to be a crook.
只要他还是个有钱的骗子，那就没关系。但我不喜欢和那些坏蛋关在一起，我不喜欢被人踢来踢去，我也受不了苏格兰的天气。
That would be all right so long as he stays a rich crook... but I don't like being caged in with all those other villains, I don't like being kicked around and I can't stand the Scottish weather.
-所以你就走了?-我游了出去。还记得吗?
- So you walked out? - I swam out. Remember?
是的。
Yeah.
留下什么都不后悔吗?
No regrets about leaving anything behind?
是的。一个非常昂贵的衣橱。
Yes. A very expensive wardrobe.
也许你加入了错误的阵营。也许我们不会赢。
Maybe you joined the wrong side. Maybe we won't come out on top.
我总能游回来。
I can always swim back.
他想见你。天啊，你看起来糟透了。我希望那不是我的咖啡。
He wants to see you. God, you look terrible. I hope it's not my coffee.
如果不坐船出海就好了。
Boats would be wonderful if only one didn't have to go to sea in them.
让她在外面跑上跑下。不要比我们靠得更近。
Keep her running up and down outside. Don't get any nearer than we are.
从直升机上掉下来?
Fall out of your helicopter?
是的。
Yeah.
欢呼。
Cheers.
很抱歉这么不正式。
Sorry about being so informal.
没什么大不了的。但下次带个女人来。
Think nothing of it. But next time bring a woman.
你的钱还不够吗?
Haven't you got enough?
光看它们没有什么乐趣。
There's no pleasure in just looking at them.
这就像吃巧克力一样。这里。
That's like eating chocolate with the paper on. Here.
不,我开车。听。我需要你的帮助。
No, I'm driving. Listen. I need your help.
我最好告诉你我是谁，我想让你为我做什么。
I'd better tell you who I am and what I want you to do for me.
如果你不再喝一杯就不会了。
Not if you don't have another drink.
看那艘船。
Look at that boat.
这里的未来。
It's coming here.
又来了。亲爱的，你来开车好吗?
Here we go again. Take the wheel, will you, dear?
你想干什么?击退寄宿生吗?
What are you trying to do? Repel all boarders?
把装备带上飞机。
Bring that gear aboard.
把它带回托贝。午夜前保持与大陆的距离。
Take it back to Torbay. Keep in sight of the mainland till midnight.
故事很精彩，亚瑟爵士，但我们会帮忙的。
It's a hell of a story, Sir Arthur, but we'll help.
不管怎样，这和捕鲨鱼有很大的不同。
Anyhow, it make a change from shark fishing.
这艘船在这一带很有名。
This boat's well known in the area.
蒂姆会带我们去杜·斯凯。我们先去那个地方……我永远念不出它的名字。坟墓之口。
Tim will take us to Du Skea. First we'll go to that place... I can never pronounce its name. Mouth of the Grave.
你永远不可能驶过那里。
You'll never sail through there.
我当然会。再来几次之后。
Of course I will. After a few more of these.
希望你没来?
Wish you hadn't come?
如果你确定这是14英寻的山脊，那就是这里。
This is it if you're sure it's this 14-fathom ledge.
它必须。这是唯一能让船沉下去的地方。
It must be. It's the only logical place where you can sink a ship.
这里有七英寻深，海床太平了，没有地方可以隐藏桅杆或烟囱。
Here at seven fathoms, the sea bed is too flat - no place to hide masts or funnels.
但在那之外，在这里，35英寻，太深，压力太大。
But beyond that, over here - 35 fathoms, too deep, too much pressure.
- 14英寻。唯一符合逻辑的地方。——祝你好运。
- 14 fathoms. The only logical place. - Good luck.
-这是香格里拉!-你们俩下去
- It's the Shangri-la! - Get below, you two.
哦，是哈钦森的船。
Oh, it's Hutchinson's boat.
是的。当地的鲨鱼渔夫。没有恐慌。没关系。
Yes. The local shark fisherman. No panic. It's all right.
是吗?
Is it?
因为到目前为止一切都不对劲，对吧?
Because nothing has been all right so far, has it?
我看他们明天之前不可能把金条卸了。
I can't see them unloading that bullion before tomorrow.
也许他们会带着他们有的东西离开。
Maybe they'll take what they've got and get out.
他们不确定我们是否知道金条的事。
They don't know for sure that we know about the bullion.
总之，我很幸运。奎恩的死看起来像是意外。
Anyway, I was lucky. Quinn's death looks like an accident.
我们到底要不要进去?
Are we going in or not?
我的兄弟们想锻炼一下。
My lads feel like a bit of exercise.
我们先去你家。
First we go back to your place.
在我确保其他人安全之后，他们会在午夜得到他们需要的所有锻炼。
They'll get all the exercise they need at midnight - after I make sure other people are safe.
你应该睡个美容觉。
You should get some beauty sleep.
你说要确保其他人的安全是什么意思?
What did you mean about making sure other people are safe?
你看起来脸色苍白。
You look pale.
你的晒黑肤色要消失了。
You're losing that jet-set tan.
你一点都不相信我，是吗?
You don't trust me one bloody inch, do you?
做一个充满阴谋的女人感觉好吗?
Does it feel good to be a woman of intrigue?
和神秘吗?
And mystery?
-你想和我做爱吗?——是的。
- Do you want to make love to me? - Yes.
-想看看瘀伤怎么样了。-他们还在那里。
- Wanted to see how the bruises were. - They're still there.
你觉得我是化妆的时候穿的吗?
Do you think I put them on with make-up?
我还是不知道它们是怎么到那里的。
I'm still not sure how they got there.
我被殴打。
I was beaten.
也许你很容易受伤。
Maybe you bruise easily.
那你在床上最好对我温柔点。
Then you'd better be very gentle with me in bed.
我会的。我甚至会脱掉我的靴子。
I will. I'll even take my boots off.
我还没了解你我一点都不相信你。
I still haven't worked you out yet and I don't trust you one bloody inch.
不管怎样，只是为了记录。
Anyway, just for the record.
你在海上待了很长时间了，是吗?
You've been a long time at sea, haven't you?
这在那些战争电影里总是管用的。
This always worked in those war movies.
看不见你。它会。那么午夜见。
Aye. It'll hold. See you at midnight then.
八个钟。欢呼。祝你好运。
Eight bells. Cheers. Good luck.
-也敬你。——谢谢。
- And to you. - Thanks.
醒来。房间服务。我想见柯克塞德小姐。
Wake up. Room service. I want to see Miss Kirkside.
移动。
Move.
这是正确的。这是我的男孩。动!
That's right. That's my boy. Move!
这是更好的。
That's better.
-你想要什么?这是怎么呢——穿好衣服。
- What do you want? What's going on? - Get dressed.
发生了什么?——移动,女孩。移动。
- What's happening? - Move, girl. Move.
-我是你穿着闪亮盔甲的骑士。-你是直升机上的那个人。
- I'm your knight in shining armour. - You're the man from the helicopter.
你有皮带吗?绳子还是什么?醒来,女孩!
Have you got a belt? A cord or something? Wake up, girl!
这做吗?你是谁?
Will this do? Who are you?
别问问题。穿上衣服。
Don't ask questions. Get some clothes on.
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
奇怪的是，我是好人。
Strangely enough, I'm one of the good guys.
也就是说我支持法律和秩序而我没有多少时间了。
Which means I'm on the side of law and order and I haven't much time.
对吧?我需要一些答案和帮助。
Right? I want some answers and I want some help.
不。请。你什么也不能做。
No. Please. You mustn't do anything.
你不能。
You mustn't.
这里有囚犯，不是吗?人质。不是吗? !
There are prisoners here, aren't there? Hostages. Aren't there?!
如果你做什么，他们就会有危险。
They'll be in danger if you do anything.
如果我不这么做，他们会更惨。
They'll be in a bloody sight more if I don't.
今晚就要出事了。
Things are going to happen tonight.
我是来把这些人赶走的。
I'm here to get these people away.
你哥哥和男朋友。
Your brother and boyfriend.
麦当劳的儿子。其他人呢?
MacDonald's sons. Anyone else?
一些渔夫和那个女人。
Some fishermen and the woman.
什么女人?
What woman?
Skouras女士。
Lady Skouras.
女士Skouras ?
Lady Skouras?
-他们在哪里?-在地牢里。
- Where are they? - In the dungeons.
-但他们被守卫着，锁着。- - - - - -来吧。
- But they're guarded and locked. - Come on.
-你得分散警卫的注意力。——如何?
- You've got to distract the guard. - How?
猜测。
Guess.
-别这样!-你想怎么样?
- Don't do that! - What do you expect?
我最不需要的就是这个，尤其是在楼梯上。
The last thing I need is that, especially on the staircase.
-分散警卫的注意力。-我该怎么办?
- Just distract the guard. - What do I do?
——就出现。剩下的就靠情欲了。-如果他不喜欢我怎么办?
- Just appear. Lust will do the rest. - What if he doesn't fancy me?
我们只需要一个同性恋狱警。请。继续。
All we need is a guard that's queer. Please. Go on.
有你吗?你有喝的吗?
Have you? Have you got a drink or something?
我可以买一些。
I could get some.
威士忌就好了。
Whisky would be nice.
感觉到热了吗?
Feeling the heat, are you?
这是加载吗?
Is it loaded?
是的。的确是。
Yeah. It sure is.
肉体的罪恶，我的朋友……从来没有支付。
Sins of the flesh, my friend... never pay.
“加载”!在高地，你不应该只会跟踪鹿。
"Is it loaded"! You must learn more than deer stalking in the Highlands.
我们为什么不上楼呢?暖和得多。Skouras女士。
Why don't we go upstairs? It's much warmer. Lady Skouras.
晚上好。
Good evening.
带大家去你的房间，把自己锁起来。
Take everyone to your room and lock yourselves in.
-你打算怎么做?-有并发症。
- What are you going to do? - There are complications.
我不知道斯古洛斯是勒索的受害者。他是我们中的一员。
I didn't realise Skouras was a blackmail victim. He's one of us.
-他们带了一个。——他是谁?
- They've got one of theirs with us. - Who's he?
不是男的，是女的。
It's not a he, it's a she.
你应该知道，哈钦森先生，我有多感激你的帮助。
You should know, Mr Hutchinson, how much I appreciate your help.
你的忠诚，责任感和公共精神在这个时代并不常见。
Your loyalty, sense of duty and public spirit one doesn't meet with often in this day and age.
你的朋友告诉我们保险公司会出多少钱。
Your mate told us how much the insurance companies would cough up.
他了吗?卡尔弗特先生不是我的“伙伴”。他和我没什么共同之处。
Did he? Mr Calvert is not my "mate". He and I have little in common.
你以前去过那里吗?你知道船库吗?
Have you been there before? Do you know the boathouse?
你知道它有多大吗?
Do you know how big it is?
看不见你。船屋门宽17英尺。
Aye. Boathouse door is 17 feet wide.
-这艘船呢?- 15英尺的横梁，没有信标。
- And this boat? - A 15-foot beam and no beacons.
我们不可能在不触礁的情况下接受它。
We can never take it in without ending up on the rocks.
只有一个办法能知道。
There's only one way to find out.
而且，你的伴侣永远不会原谅我的。
Besides, your mate would never forgive me.
把它。
Take it.
我懂了。看。
I've got it. Watch it.
稳定。
Steady.
把重量。
Take the weight.
把它。小心!
Bring it up. Careful!
好的。停。拥有一切。做好准备。
All right. Stop. Hold everything. Get ready.
别让别人看见你!快!
Get out of sight! Quick!
快点!
Hurry up!
在这里。杜Skea城堡。
There it is. Du Skea castle.
不要动!你四周都有掩护!
Don't move! You're covered on all sides!
放下枪!
Put down those guns!
缓慢。
Slowly.
就是这样。谢谢你！
That's it. Thank you.
我很抱歉。恐怕我们擅自闯入了。
I'm so sorry. I'm afraid we're trespassing.
是的,你是。我相信卡尔弗特就在这里的某个地方。
Yes, you are. I believe Calvert is loose somewhere in the grounds.
我妻子很晚才留下最后一条无线电信息。
My wife left her last radio message rather late.
——你的妻子吗?-去爱、尊敬和服从。
- Your wife? - To love, honour and obey.
你知道的。
You know how it goes.
别挡道，亲爱的。我不想让你受伤。
Get out of the way, darling. I don't want you to get hurt.
不!拜托!
No! Please!
-你犯了一个严重的错误——好的。
- You're making a terrible mistake. - All right.
——Charnley。Charnley !-劳埃德的查恩利勋爵?
- Charnley. Get Charnley! - Lord Charnley of Lloyds?
是的!
Yes!
我的上帝，没有什么是神圣的。
My God, there's nothing sacred.
哈钦森,阻止他!
Hutchinson, stop him!
你抓到他了?做得很好。我只是来帮忙的。
Oh, you got him then? Well done. I was just coming to lend a hand.
-他跟这事无关——什么?
- He had nothing to do with it. - Nothing?
当然可以。我一直都是这么说的，不是吗?
Of course. That's what I always said, wasn't it?
女孩在哪里?
Where's the girl?
不知道她知不知道自己是个寡妇。原谅我。
I wonder if she knows she's a widow. Excuse me.
啊，你来了。
Ah, there you are.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
你觉得你哪儿也去不了，对吧?
You don't think you're going anywhere, do you?
你没有和我吻别。
You didn't kiss me goodbye.
我会写。每一天。
I would have written. Every day.
-来自阳光明媚的阿卡普尔科或其他地方。-或者从监狱里。
- From sunny Acapulco or somewhere. - Or from prison.
你确实交了些坏朋友。
You do keep rather bad company.
我只是在做一个忠诚的妻子。
I was only being a loyal wife.
现在你要做一个忠诚的寡妇了。
And now you're going to be a loyal widow.
然后我就可以开始新的生活。
Then I can make a new start in life.
也许和你一起…和什么?
Perhaps with you and... And what?
下面有一些金子。
Some of that gold down there.
也许。谁知道呢?
Perhaps. Who knows?
卡尔弗特有个主意……卡尔弗特和我有个主意，想找出这次船运灾难的保险公司。
Calvert had the idea... Calvert and I had the idea of finding out the underwriters of your shipping disaster.
-我从没想过查恩利勋爵。——是的。Charnley。
- I never thought of Lord Charnley. - Yes. It was Charnley.
我被勒索了。
I was being blackmailed.
他们需要我的资金，需要我的掩护。
They needed my finance and they needed my cover.
但当他们带走我的妻子安娜时，我别无选择，只能跟着他们走。没有选择。
But when they took Anna, my wife, I had no choice but to go along with them. No choice.
我知道它。一个人对这些事情有一种本能。
I knew it. One has an instinct about these things.
我们葡萄酒委员会的成员。
A member of our wine committee.
我告诉卡尔弗特了，但他不听。
I told Calvert but he wouldn't listen.
卡尔弗特的问题在于他不是个真正的绅士。
The trouble with Calvert is he's not really a gentleman.
他去了哪里?
Where did he get to?
——只有一个?-你感受过它们的重量吗?
- Only one? - Have you felt the weight of them?
这将让你在阿卡普尔科的酒店里享受五年的奢华生活——只要你不经常使用客房服务。
That'll keep you in luxury in a hotel Acapulco for five years - so long as you don't use room service too much.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
这都是你的。我不喜欢太阳。
It's all yours. I don't like the sun.
-让我得了花粉热。-你想让我留下吗?
- Gives me hay fever. - Do you want me to stay?
我不想让你变成一个诚实的女人。
I didn't want to make an honest woman out of you.
我不认为我们生活在幸福的家庭里。你呢?
I don't see us living in domestic bliss. Do you?
不。晚上会很好，但白天就会很累人。
No. The nights would be good but the days would be a drag.
嗯,一路顺风。
Well, bon voyage.
不要一次花光。
Don't spend it all at once.
没有你我怎么可能离开这里?
What chance have I of getting out of here without you?
不多，但有机会。
Not much, but a chance.
你只担心你的工作，而且你要做好。
All you're worried about is your job and you do it right.
这就是你要做的。你就是个职业混蛋。
That's all you do. You're just a professional bastard.
用我一位已故朋友的话来说…这是我擅长的。
In the words of a late friend of mine... it's what I do well.